(Penny:)If you really
care that much,
(Howard:)there are apps now that'll let
you hire people to do stuff
(Howard:)like errands and
wait in lines.
(Stuart:)People are actually
waiting in lines as a job?
(Stuart:)Boy, makes me feel better
about my life.
(Howard:)Some of these guys make
over $20 an hour.
(Stuart:)And now I feel worse again.
(Beverly:)I'm not surprised Leonard
chose to avoid picking me up.
(Beverly:)He's battled intimacy issues
his whole life.
(Beverly:)Does he have difficulty
maintaining erections?
(Penny:)Wow.
(clears throat)
(Penny:)Didn't even make it
out of the parking lot.
(Penny:)Uh, you know what,
enough about Leonard.
(Penny:)Let's talk about you.
(Penny:)What would you like to
do while you're here?
(Beverly:)Dear, I'm a psychiatrist.
(Beverly:)You don't have to avoid having
intimate conversations with me.
(Penny:)Well, I'd actually like
for us to be close,
(Penny:)but maybe we start
with our favorite books
(Penny:)and work our way up
to my husband's sex organs.
(Beverly:)Very well.
(Beverly:)What's the last book
you read?